Sad...
Unbelievably sad...
Again...
That dream again...
Am I...
crying?
It's him!
Sad...
Am I laughing again?
Was I hit?
Today...
I will see.
Just a bit more...
Just...
a bit more and...
That dream...
That dream again...
Vincent,
where are you?
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
meditation    leap into the void
What's wrong?
I'm sure Iggy's still being watched by Grandfather.
Nothing.
Hey, Re-l.
About this...
The Information Bureau's databank was accessed seventy-four times?
Not to mention, only encrypted
accounts, all within this short time period.
Isn't that strange?
That's true.
Logging in with the highest possible access level...
It'd be reasonable to assume that it was the Security Bureau.
Want me to handle it?
And what was their purpose?
This is...
Dorothy...
This way, Vincent.
Where are you?
She's that...
Dorothy...
This way, Vincent.
No!
Wait...
Damn...
Why?
Why me?
Damn!
Target lost.
Updated input of target's projected escape trajectory,
commencing.
To think that we are still unable to pinpoint his location.
How can you not control him?
Everything leads back to us.
We have no excuse.
We have no time to lose.
Be fully aware of that.
Relieve us of our anxiety as soon as possible.
You may be replaced before your term is over.
After all, there are as many
Entourage-type autoreivs as there are stars in the sky.
Understood.
Chief, I can't find it!
Be thorough in your search!
It's not your average infected autoreiv!
If we catch it, we might get special promotions!
What are you doing here?
Are you a companion-type?
You're...
If I remember correctly,
your name is Pino.
Pino?
Where are you,
Vincent Law?
Hey, hey.
Is Pino me?
Is it okay for Pino to be me?
Hey.
So I think I'm-
Don't speak so loudly!
A facial expression app, huh.
That's why companion-type autoreivs are...
Stay there, okay?
Okay?
Just stay
sitting there for a while.
'Kay.
That's...
This?
Don't answer it!
Hello?
Who's this?
Is that you, Vincent?
Inspector Re-l...
Where are you now?
Dorothy was...
It was the armed autoreivs...
It wasn't me.
They...
It was a trap!
Everything is-
Get a hold of yourself!
I wonder why things turned out like this.
If I stay here...
Please save me.
I...
I don't have anyone else I can turn to.
What can you see there?
I have to run.
Light rail trains are crossing...
Beyond this point...
You're planning to leave through a plugvent?
l don't care anymore.
If I'm really done for,
I might as well go outside-
What awaits you outside is a world of death.
It doesn't seem like I can become a model citizen.
Vincent!
I'm glad I could hear your voice one last time.
I'll go to the plugvent as well.
Wait until I get there.
Vincent!
Dammit!
What the...
hell?
Damn!
Let's find another route.
You don't need this?
It's heavy.
Wait, wait!
The Security Bureau, huh.
This place isn't any good either.
Is this place a maze or what?
Please give me the bag.
I'll need to use something as a light...
Pino?
Pino!
This way.
That thing...
She knows where to go?
Information Bureau Agent Re-l,
where are you headed in such a hurry?
It seems your Entourage is not with you.
I'm going to inspect a crime scene
in the immigrant residential sectors.
My Entourage is following me fifteen minutes behind.
Pardon me then.
Please be careful.
So autoreivs infected by the cogito virus
were all trying to flee in the same direction.
I guess none of this matters now.
It's a dead end.
Hey!
Her instincts are too sharp.
I wonder who she gets it from.
All citizens are based on synchronized information.
Localized approximations are insignificant.
I knew we shouldn't have assigned her to the Information Bureau.
No, it was an appropriate decision
from an educational perspective as well.
As proof, she possessed the highest sensitivity at the citizen level.
The results are excellent.
However, the resulting ability to
take action is the cause behind it all.
Cause?
What about the Security Bureau?
There is no need for concern.
We made it quite clear to him.
In any case,
it cannot be denied that Romdeau's stability is weakening.
We must take rapid measures
to resolve the situation.
If we do not-
Our raison d'être will be destroyed.
That is our sole source of anxiety.
You're here, aren't you, Vincent?
I'm here alone.
I don't have anything on me now.
Wait!
Hello.
Come out, Vincent!
Inspector Re-l,
I...
Vincent Law,
why are you wanted by the Security Bureau?!
Inspector...
What did you see in my bathroom?!
Answer me!
Bathroom?
How do you explain this?
Why...
do you have that?
You know already, don't you?
That...
monster...
What did you see?!
Wh-What did I see?
I was attacked suddenly at the mall!
Then the Security Bureau came after me!
Inspector,
I didn't do anything.
But why?
You saw the monster?
You also saw...
PROXY?
Vincent Law,
don't move!
Do exactly as we say.
So, the Security Bureau.
Re-l Mayer!
Vincent, it's not what you think!
What isn't?!
Outside!
Crap!
Vince!
Iggy, Vincent's-!
You silly girl!
Vincent!
I've always...
tried to become a model citizen,
suppressing who I am...
putting up a front...
I've been trying desperately...
all the time...
no matter where I am.
Vincent!
And the end result of it all... is this?
I am a failure, that's what.
Vincent...
Listen!
I'll talk to my grandfather!
I won't let the Security Bureau lay a finger on you either!
Never doubting the system...
and following all the rules...
Those are the prerequisites for becoming a model citizen.
Don't go!
I...
don't think I can ever become a model citizen.
Not even at the very end.
Why are you closing the plugvent?
Capture and arrest him!
Further exposure
will endanger the entire city.
Vincent!
He...
It's over...
Everything...
is over.
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
A man missing, gone into the darkness,
and a path into the remaining labyrinth.
Ulterior motives that writhe behind the scenes of the utopia
meditation  sing the future, future of hades
beckon the lost ones to Hades.